Stand your ground.
Green Street Hooligans is a crime, drama film directed by Lexi Alexander.
After being wrongfully expelled from Harvard University, American
Matt Buckner flees to his sister's home in England.
Once there, he is befriended by her charming and dangerous brother-in-law, Pete
Dunham, and introduced to the underworld of British football hooliganism.
Matt learns to stand his ground through a friendship that develops
against the backdrop of this secret and often violent world.
'Green Street Hooligans' is a story of loyalty, trust and the
sometimes brutal consequences of living close to the edge.
Matt Buckner, played by Elijah Wood.
Pete Dunham, played by Charlie Hunnam.
Shannon Dunham, played by Claire Forlani.
Steve Dunham, played by Marc Warren.
Bovver, played by Leo Gregory.
Tommy Hatcher, played by Geoff Bell.
Green Street Hooligans (also known as Green Street and Hooligans) is a 2005
crime drama film about football hooliganism in the United Kingdom.
The film is directed by Lexi Alexander and stars Elijah Wood, Charlie
Hunnam, Claire Forlani, Marc Warren, and Leo Gregory.
Two sequels followed in the form of direct-to-video releases.
The first, Green Street 2: Stand Your Ground, was released on various
dates around the world between March 2009 to July 2010.
The second, Green Street 3: Never Back Down, was
released in the UK on 21 October 2013.
The film explores themes of london, england, sports,
harvard university, hooligan, revenge.
The tone is dark and emotional.